spi-global.com 2014-04-02

# Privacy Statement | SPi Global

SPi Global (the “Company”) is committed to maintaining your confidence and trust with respect to the privacy of the personally identifiable information we collect from you. We also believe that the efficient collection, use and transfer of information serve to enhance the development of the Internet and electronic commerce, provided that such information is handled in a fair and responsible manner. We believe that the establishment of trust and privacy is instrumental to the continued growth of the Internet.

**Scope of this Privacy Statement**

SPi Global is one of the world’s largest and most diversified Knowledge Process Outsourcing (KPO), Health Care and Customer Relationship Management (CRM) service providers in the industry in terms of clients, geographic presence, and capabilities with legal entities that cross borders. This Privacy Statement applies to all services of SPi Global website and sub-sites available under the domain SPi-Global.com

**How We Collect Personal Information**

The Company receives personal data in several ways. The information collected directly from a user may include contact information such as the user's name, e-mail address, postal address and other personal information to register for a subscription or a service, so that we can later contact you regarding an inquiry, to process an order, to be considered for employment or to do business with us.

The Company may also collect information relating to your use of our web sites through the use of various technologies including “cookies” which allow us to determine, for example, your IP address, browser type, access time and/or viewed pages within our website.

  * **Cookies.** We use cookies on this site. A “cookie” is a piece of data that a website can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your computer as a tag that identifies your computer. While cookies are often only used to measure website usage and effectiveness and to allow for ease of navigation or use and as such, are not associated with any personal information, they are also used at times to personalize a known visitor's experience to a website by being associated with profile information or user preferences. By using our website, you agree to the placing of cookies on your device. 

You can set your browser in most instances to notify you before you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it or not. You can also generally set your browser to turn off cookies.

**How Personal Information Is Used**

We use the personal information that you provide for such purposes as:

  * **Recruitment:** If you submit a resume via e-mail or job application online, we will use your Personal Data for recruitment-related purposes, which may include contacting you via e-mail, telephone or post. Except where you request otherwise, SPi Global may keep your Personal Data on file for an appropriate time in order to consider you for other employment opportunities with SPi Global in the future.
  * **Communicating with you:** We will follow up on comments and other requests that you submit to us through our website, such as online queries or emailing us. This may include calling you back by telephone or communicating with you via email.
  * **Direct marketing and promotion:** Direct marketing and/or promotional efforts by or on behalf of SPi Global may include providing you with specific information that you have requested online or providing more general information about other SPi Global offerings. When we collect Personal Data for direct marketing or promotional purposes, however, we generally offer you appropriate choices regarding the use of your Personal Data.

**How We Share Your Information**

We share your personal information with authorize third parties only in the ways that are described in this Privacy Statement. We do not sell, trade, rent or distribute personal information to any outside person or organization.

You should note that the Company is a global organization with business processes, management structures and technical systems that cross borders. As such, we may share information about you within our corporate group of companies and transfer it to countries in the world where we do business in connection with the uses identified above and in accordance with this Privacy Statement. Our Privacy Statement and our practices are designed to provide a globally consistent level of protection for personal information.

**Legal Disclosures**

SPi Global may disclose your Personal Data in order to enforce our website Terms of Use or in urgent circumstances to protect personal safety, the public or SPi Global website. It is also possible that we may be required by law to disclose your Personal Data pursuant to judicial or other government subpoenas, warrants, or orders, potentially, in any country where we do business.

**Business Reorganizations**

Like many organizations, SPi Global may reorganize its business operations around the world from time to time, whether by buying new businesses or selling or merging existing businesses. This may involve us disclosing Personal Data to prospective or actual purchasers of parts of our business, or receiving personal data from potential sellers. It is our practice to seek appropriate confidentiality protection for Personal Data disclosed in these types of transactions.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions or suggestions about this Privacy Statement or the Company's handling of your information, you may [contact us here](http://www.spi-global.com/contact-us).

**Notification of Changes**

If there is any material change in the way we use, collect or disclose personal information, and updated Privacy Statement we may notify you by e-mail (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. In order to check updates to this Privacy Statement, please consult this page on a regular basis. If we are going to use your personal information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify you either as indicated above, by directly sending you a notification or both, at our option, and you will have a choice as to whether or not we can use your personal information in such a way.
